<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<HAR_Outerm.label>Outerm</HAR_Outerm.label>
	<HAR_Outerm.description>Outerms are a kind of artificial race that has only begun appearing across the cosmos in recent years.\nThey are marked by an eerily glowing crimson halo and twisted, warped crowlike wings.\nNo records of them exist in the databases of Canaan, the homeworld of the artificial races, and much about them remains a mystery.\n\nLike other artificial races, they grow stronger as time passes,\nand acquire a variety of uncanny powers as they advance through each stage.\n\nThey possess a decadent sensibility that delights in blood-pumping violence and drowning lust, making them intensely aggressive.\nThey despise rigid order and law, favoring corruption and decadence instead.\nPerhaps because they live for the moment, they seem strangely detached from both life and death.\n\nAt the same time, they are deeply devout, worshipping the faceless god known as the \"Void's ■■■.\"\nWhatever form the divine command takes, they gladly obey it, even at the cost of their own lives.\n\nIn the underworld they have built the syndicate known as Haos, ruling drifters and criminals through drugs and violence.\nWith divine guidance, abundant funds, and plentiful resources, their influence seems to keep spreading even now.\n\nOuterms are innately incapable of reproduction and cannot bear children.\nHow they continue to increase their numbers without any production plants of their own remains shrouded in darkness.\n\n\n\n\nGood arrives in the wake of evil.\nAs if paving a bloodstained road into one fit for humankind.</HAR_Outerm.description>
	<HAR_Outerm.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.bodyAddons.0.name>wings</HAR_Outerm.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.bodyAddons.0.name>
	<HAR_Outerm.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.bodyAddons.1.name>halo</HAR_Outerm.alienRace.generalSettings.alienPartGenerator.bodyAddons.1.name>
	<HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_a.commandLabel>Vrykolakas</HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_a.commandLabel>
	<HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_a.commandDesc>Bites and drains blood from a single target.\nActivation requirement: Artificial Race Lv 1\nReuse time: 30 minutes</HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_a.commandDesc>
	<HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_b.commandLabel>Hyperetes</HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_b.commandLabel>
	<HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_b.commandDesc>Summons three frenzied crows.\nActivation requirement: Artificial Race Lv 2\nReuse time: 3 hours</HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_b.commandDesc>
	<HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_c.commandLabel>Akinoia</HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_c.commandLabel>
	<HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_c.commandDesc>Enters a state of chance-based evasion.\nActivation requirement: Artificial Race Lv 3\nReuse time: 1 day</HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_c.commandDesc>
	<HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_d.commandLabel>Catalysis</HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_d.commandLabel>
	<HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_d.commandDesc>Temporarily paralyzes part of a single target's functions.\nActivation requirement: Artificial Race Lv 4\nReuse time: 1 hour</HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_d.commandDesc>
	<HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_e.commandLabel>Apostolos</HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_e.commandLabel>
	<HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_e.commandDesc>Receives power from a higher plane and enters an empowered state.\nActivation requirement: Artificial Race Lv 5\nReuse time: 3 days</HAR_Outerm.comps.HAR_OT_Comp_Skill_e.commandDesc>
</LanguageData>
